

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







SAFe 5 Scrum Master seeking roles in IT Project Management, Portfolio Management, PMO Operations, Stakeholder Management, Application Support, Risk Management, Incident Management, Business

Continuity, ServiceNow, Confluence, Jira, Java, JSP, WCS, JUnit, Oracle

Current Designation: Service Delivery Manager Total Experience: 16 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Project Mar-IT/Software

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Scrum Master, Project Manager-IT/Software, IT Project Management, Portfolio Management, PMO Operations, Stakeholder Management, Application Support, Risk Management, Incident Management, Business Continuity, Service Now, Confluence, Jira, Java, JSP, WCS, JUnit, Oracle

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Experienced Service Delivery Manager with over 15 years of experience in IT applications development and implementation across multiple geographical locations in APAC region. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving improvements. Technical competency along with Agile Project Management and IT Service Management (ITSM) experience.

Work Experience

Infosys as Scrum Master -IT, Service Delivery Manager Nov 2010 to Mar 2020

Develop, plan and deliver the portfolio of work for major transformation projects valued at 5M+ as per Scrum framework

Conduct daily scrum standups, scrum ceremonies, iteration & backlog planning, effort estimation sessions, and retrospective analysis for different projects Maintain Kanban boards for project running on Kanban framework

Co-ordinate dependencies with other teams and remove risks for delivering on time Lead and coach team on agile methodologies to build maturity in agile practices Implement DevOps practices and automated testing for each release

Build relationships with all stakeholders including product owners and provide weekly reports Ensure deliverables are of quality standards at end of each sprint

Service Delivery Manager Dec 2016 - March 2020 NBN Co. (Infosys Australia) Melbourne, VIC

Deliver changes to business-critical applications covered under NBN Workforce/Assurance platform including Maximo, Workforce Microservices & APIs, Remedy, BPPM

Lead production support and maintenance activities

Manage customer relationships to provide high service availability

Deliver change requests and ensure SLA compliance for production issues

Coordinate with multiple teams including customer's 3rd party vendors and delivery partners for end to end resolution of issues

Project management - ensure that all contractual obligation agreed in SOW are met, Work

breakdown, allocation and management of workload within team Project planning - create project briefs with feature backlogs, delivery milestones, scope,

RAID, effort estimation, cost and financial summary Assist and participate in Pre-sales activities including drafting RFP / RFQ / RFI responses

Perform monthly calculations and reporting of Service Levels and budget

Lead support engagements and administer the PMO activities

Maintain the JIRA dashboard and align with scrum agile delivery model

Define ITIL process maps, address any gaps in support model, and evolve the support

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

processes and methodologies

Manage and co-ordinate between onshore and offshore resources to ensure 24x7 support and smooth transition between various time zones

Ensure delivery of support from a time, cost and quality perspective

Draft statement of work (SoW) to include requirements, scope, milestones, acceptance criteria and pricing structure

Provide detailed reviews of service disruptions, metrics - Ensure that the SLA and KPIs are met as committed to customer in MSA

Perform periodic reviews with customer for improvements - Drive productivity improvement and efficiencies across the teams

Plan and execute the cloud migration strategy - manage the migration of on-premise applications to AWS cloud

Initiate and be involved in the change and release management process of the customer's environment to ensure success and service uptime

Manage monthly releases as per Release Change Requests (RCR) and drive approvals with Change Approval Board (CAB)

Co-ordinate and facilitate Performance Testing, SIT and UAT before Go Live

Liaise with multiple stakeholders including vendors and customers to implement changes in production as per run sheet during Go Live

Deliver change communications to all impacted stakeholders and send regular status updates to management

Drive root cause analysis for issues and co-ordinate with various internal and external vendor teams including Infrastructure, Development, Oracle DBA, Testing, and Change Management Be self-driven and work independently to manage costs, team, SLA compliance and client management with minimum supervision and guidance from practice leaders

Project Manager Oct 2015 - Nov 2016

Maxis Telecom (Infosys Malaysia) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Production Support and Maintenance

Handling production issues and resolving incidents as per service agreements

Manage onsite and offshore teams of around 30 members giving 24x7 support to various key applications for client

Requirements gathering, Business Analysis, Change Impact Assessments for Enhancements & Change Requests

Infosys as Service Delivery Manager

Nov 2010 to Till Date

Aricent Technologies as Senior Developer

Sep 2006 to Oct 2010

Requirements Gathering and Impact Analysis with the customer

Designing of the UI for the assigned modules

Implementing of the Business Logic for those modules based on Layer wise component design Distributing the activities among the team members and keeping track of progress on work Release Management activities

Technology: Java, J2EE, JSF with Validation Framework, Tomcat, XML, ClearCase, Ant, Eclipse, ClearQuest, Apache, Purify, Quantify

SLK Software India as Software Developer

Aug 2004 to Sep 2006

Designing of the UI for the assigned modules using the struts framework

Creating UTCs of the Sites, Product Alert and News modules

Implementing of the Business Logic for those modules based on Layer wise component design Designing, documenting and prototyping of the maintain User, search order, admin features, maintain sales org codes of the application using the struts framework

Implementing the code for assigned modules

Unit testing the code developed

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from Manipal Institute of Technology (MIT) in 2004

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
ServiceNow	
CONFLUENCE	
JIRA	
Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint	
Java, JSP	
WCS, JUnit	
ORACLE 10G	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Kannada				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.